

Emmanuel Gómez

I'm an 4 years old experienced web developer, with knowledge in Javascript, and their frameworks Angular, Node, React, Vue and Express. I have known how to implement APIs, and deploy a hybrid web app with iOnic. I consider myself as a determined, diligent, trustworthy and a self-starter person. Also I have an interest in increasing my social network.

Education

- Computational Systems Engineering,UVEG,
- C1 Advanced, CENLEX

Experience

T&C Group- Front End Developer (2017 - 2018)

Freelancer - Fullstack Developer (2018 - 2019)

Grupo Nach - Database Administrator (2019-2020)

CIHUMANA - Fullstack Developer (2020 - 2021)

Skills

- Angular 3 años
- Vue JS 1 año
- Java 3 años
- Spring 1 año
- Node 1.5 años
- Express JS 1 año
- Git 2 año
- SQL 3 años
- React 1 año
- Bootstrap 2 años

Selected Past Work

T&C Group - Front End Developer:

- Web development in frontend, javascript validations and forms.
- SPA maintenance

Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Freelancer - Fullstack Developer:

- API Implementation
- Javascript form validation, data usage in components TS

Technologies: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap

CIHUMANA - Fullstack Developer:

- CRUD Implementation, components validation, lazy loading modules charge
- Directives use in HTML with component connection
- Routing configuration, components charge by lazy loading
- API Implementation in NodeJS with Interface use

Technologies: HTML, CSS, Angular, Node, GQL, Bootstrap, Angular Materials